<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RPermissions</string>

    <string name="show_camera">Show camera preview</string>
    <string name="camera_unavailable"><b>Camera could not be opened.</b>\nThis occurs when the camera is not available (for example it is already in use) or if the system has denied access (for example when camera access has been disabled).</string>
    <string name="intro">This sample shows a basic implementation for requesting permissions at runtime.\nClick the button below to request the Camera permission and open a full-screen camera preview.</string>
    <string name="open_camera_preview">Open Camera Preview</string>
    <string name="intro_message"><![CDATA[
This sample shows a basic implementation for requesting permissions at runtime. Click the button to
request the Camera permission and open a full-screen camera preview.

Note: The "RuntimePermissions" sample provides a more complete overview over the runtime permission
features available.]]>
    </string>
    <string name="camera_access_required">Camera access is required to display the camera preview.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_not_available">Permission is not available. Requesting camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_available">Camera permission is available. Starting preview.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_granted">Camera permission was granted. Starting preview.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_denied">Camera permission request was denied.</string>

    <string name="permision_available_contacts">Contacts Permissions have been granted. Contacts screen can now be opened.</string>
    <string name="permission_contacts_rationale">Contacts permissions are needed to demonstrate access.</string>

    <string name="contacts_string">Total number of contacts: %1$,d\nFirst contact:<b>%2$s</b></string>
    <string name="contacts_none">No contacts stored on device.</string>
    <string name="contacts_empty">Contacts not loaded.</string>
    <string name="add_contact">Add a contact</string>
    <string name="show_contact">Show first contact</string>
    <string name="contacts_intro">This fragment demonstrates access to the contact database on the device.\n
            Clicking \"Add a contact\" adds a new contact named "__DUMMY ENTRY" directly into the database.\n
    Clicking \"Show first contact\" accesses the contact database to display the name of the first contact.</string>

    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="show_contacts">Show and add contacts</string>
    <string name="main_introduction">Click the buttons below to show a camera preview or access the contacts database.\nNote that the contacts option is only available on Android M to illustrate the use of optional, M-only permissions that are not requested on lower SDK platforms.</string>

</resources>
